Welcome back! In this section, you learned
about some common project management tools
that are helpful for
communicating with your team.
You also learned about the importance
of effective meetings,
how to create a meeting agenda, and
the common types of meetings
that you'll organize, and
facilitate as a project manager.
And we discussed how you can increase
your chances of achieving a project's
goals if you develop
successful strategies for
keeping everyone informed about
the project status and major updates.
Kudos, you've completed this module,
nice job.
Coming up,
you'll learn all about the final phase of
project management: closing the project.